Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers 1966-2000 MSS 156
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - Title: Debriefing: A Reading by Susan Sontag, 5/27/1979 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0145)
      Annotations: Debriefing: A Reading by Susan Sontag.
    - Title: Ambient #1: Music For Airports - Brian Eno, 1978 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0146)
      Annotations: Ambient #1 Music For Airports Brian Eno PVC 7908 (AMB 001)
    - Title: Y Pants: Beat It Down (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0147)
      Credit info: Producer: Wharton Tiers
      Annotations: Y Pants: Beat It Down
    - Title: Tunings: R. Buckminster Fuller (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0148)
      Annotations: R. Buckminster Fuller Tunings
    - Title: Electronic Parrot, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0048)
      Format: Audiocassette
      Capacity: 90 minutes
      Annotations: (on container:)Electronic Parrot / (on cassette:)Side 1: Reese visits Paul DeMarinas + his Electronic Parrot and makes a letter to Andrea accompanied by Mozart // Side 2: The Electronic Parrot at Work
    - Title: Except That They Are Rocks '78, [1978] (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0049)
      Annotations: (on container and cassette:) except that they are rocks / 78
    - Title: G.B. Songs; 9/1974 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0050)
      Annotations: (on container:) G.B. Songs 9/74 // (on cassette:) 1/ Pretty Ma (11/74) 2. The Way That You Are Mine (9/1974) 3. I Just Want To Bleed
    - Title: Andrea Singing Spring '76 Into New Songs Spring '77, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0051)
      Annotations: (on container:)Field Guide To Birds // (on cassette:) Andrea Singing Spring '76 into New Songs Spring Spring '77
    - Title: Win + Dan 1973, 6/21/1973 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0052)
      Annotations: (on container:) Win. Dan 73 // (on cassette:) Win + Dan Carol + Reese 6-21-73
    - Title: Questions, Messages, and Jazz, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0053)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Questions Messages + Jazz
    - Title: Beached in Villages of Mobile Homes; 1977 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0054)
      Annotations: Beached in Villages of Mobile Homes; 1977 // Beached in a M.B.
    - Title: Heaven Rock Harp, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0055)
      Annotations: (on container:) Terry Fox Various Excerpts // (on cassette:) Heaven Rock Harp
    - Title: Noise Fest, June 1981 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0056)
      Credit info: Executive producer: Joshua Baer
      Annotations: Noise Fest. (titles list in container)
    - Title: A.) MR 1/30/79 Hospital exp. B.) Musac, 1979 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0057)
      Annotations: (on cassette: ) A.) MR 1/30/79 Hospital exp. B.) Musac
    - Title: Doctor / Dentist Tape "79, 1979 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0058)
      Annotations: (on container:) Doctors + Dentist Tape Feb 79// (on cassette:) A. Callard c. Feb 1979
    - Title: Registration Fire Missions: High Burst Registration, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0059)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Registration Fire Missions: High Burst Registration. Lesson #250-061-6334-E // TeleGeneral
    - Title: Circular Commotion #3, 1984 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0060)
      Annotations: Circular Commotion #3 //// c. 1984 Circle Arts, Inc.
    - Title: Red Rakes Wyoming, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0061)
      Annotations: (on container:) Red Rake Wyoming // (on cassette:) Red Rake experiments / Wyom descriptions
    - Title: A Rambling, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0062)
      Capacity: 45 minutes
      Annotations: (on container:) A Rambling // (on cassette:) 0-219 A Rambling Dear Carol…Health club
    - Title: Sun Ra 8/14/79 Squat thr, 8/14/1979 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0063)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Sun Ra 8/14/79 Squat thr
    - Title: Loop for Subway Hole (Winter '74), 1974 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0064)
      Annotations: (on container:) Loop for Subway Hole (Winter '74) 73-4 Loop noise for subway// (on cassette:) Some noise AC
    - Title: [1]-- Maritime Songs [2]-- Church Bells 1976 July 7 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0065)
      Capacity: 40 minutes
      Annotations: (on container:) Maritime Songs/ Church Bells 1976 July 7 // (on cassette:) Side 1: Maritime Songs Side 2: Church Bells
    - Title: [1]-- F.K. Song Gift '77 [2]-- Sawing, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0066)
      Annotations: (on container:) F.K. song gift 77; Sawing // (on cassette:) Side A: Some songs for Andrea from Fred 1977 Side B: Saw Sounds from A. Dec 2, 1978
    - Title: [1]-- Alanthus Reading [2]-- A Talking Ailanthus, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0067)
      Annotations: (on cassette) Side A: Alanthus reading Side B: A talking Ailanthus
    - Title: 11 thru 12 Sound Copy, [1977] (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0068)
      Alternate title: 11-12: gloves, bunk beds, electricity, small thoughts bogged down
      Annotations: (on container:) 11-12 / gloves - bunk beds - electric - bogged down - sm. thots // (on cassette:) A: A/R Cassette Test May '77 - gloves, bunk beds, electricity, small thoughts, bogged down
    - Title: Radio Music, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0069)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Radio Music
    - Title: AC Wild Bill, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0070)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) AC Wild Bill
    - Title: Untitled, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0071)
      Annotations: No annotations
    - Title: Monica at Senate 12-21-7?, [197?] (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0072)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) 0-402 Monica at Senate 12-21-7?
    - Title: Ideal Bathtub Words, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0073)
      Capacity: 45 miutes
      Annotations: (on container:) Ideal Bathtub // (on cassette:) A: 0-177 Hello Ideal Bathtub Words / b: Goodnight - 55 GB to RW then, Mack meets Lois
    - Title: Field Guide to Birds, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0074)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Field Guide to Birds // Callard, A.
    - Title: [1]-- Bruised Knees [2]-- Radio Africa, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0075)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: bruised knees B: Radio Africa
    - Title: [Hunniy; Keep Crying], Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0076)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) 1: [hunniy] 2: Keep Crying 1/2 Way
    - Title: [1]-- A Talking Ailanthus [2]-- Word Notes 5, May '77 [3]-- Auto-Bio-Underwater '77, 1977 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0077)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: A Talking Ailanthus // A: Word Notes 5, May '77 / B: Auto-Bio-Underwater '77
    - Title: Untitled (Endless Tape), Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0078)
      Capacity: 60 seconds
      Alternate Title:
    - Title: Untitled, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0079)
    - Title: Fresh, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0080)
      Annotations: (on container:) [sent by] Susan Stoltz 495 Broome Street NYC 10013 [mailed to:] Andrea Callard Bullard Mills Center South William St. Malone, NY 12950 // (on cassette:) Fresh
    - Title: Chris and Sue Jones; Winter '73, 1973 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0081)
      Annotations: (on container:) C/S Jones 73 // (on cassette:) A: Chris + Sue Jones had no heat one night and came over to sleep, drink wine + tell stories. Winter '73 B: C Jones Generally Boring
    - Title: [1]-- Chinese New Year 2/1974 [2]-- Painting Paper (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0082)
      Annotations: (on container:) Chinese New Year/ Paint Paper 74 // (on cassette:) 1:) 0-221 Chinese New Year, A Walk Thu 2/74 / 2:) Painting Paper
    - Title: Williams - Venetian Room, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0083)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) 1: Notes from Ventitian Room - Ideas obsolete + [scapped] already unfortunately. / 2: Interview at the Venitian Room With Irregular Clock and [Ideal] Garden
    - Title: JVC - Demo tape, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0084)
      Annotations: (on container:) JVC Demo -- Walon Jennings Dolly Parton, etc. / (on cassette:) JVC Demonstration Tape (orchestra selections)
    - Title: [1]-- Chanteuse; A Singing Evening with Sally White [2]-- Mitch Corber- Infinitessimus; a New Op-Op Opera, [1]-- 7/1983 [2]-- 1984 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0085)
      Annotations: (on container) Chanteuse; A Singing Evening with Sally White / Mitch Corber- Infinitessimus; a New Op-Op Opera // (on cassette:) Sally White at Tin Pan Alley w/ Mitch at elec.piano
    - Title: [1]-- Finch Mech; Birds [2]-- Dishes, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0086)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Side 1: Finch Mech "Birds" / Side 2: Dishes
    - Title: Tounge + Groove '76 - fragment, 1976 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0087)
      Annotations: (on container:) fragment tongue + groove '76 / (on cassette:) I hv torchured some of the toungs
    - Title: Consumer Blues '77 - fragment, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0088)
      Annotations: (on container:) fragment consumer blues '77 / (on cassette:) photo consumer/ b.queen (garb)
    - Title: Struk By Trucks, 7/ 1979 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0089)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Struk by Trucks 2:45 / July 79
    - Title: [Krank], Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0090)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) [KRANK]??
    - Title: Friday at Clarissa's; Feb. 18, 1983, 2/18/1983 (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0091)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Friday at Clarissa's; Feb. 18, 1983 Side 1, Clarissa, Helga, Susan and later Trisssy / Side 2 - Helga, Clarissa, Trissy, Susan
    - Title: [1]-- Score for a Lunch [2]-- Dora Reese + Bob Dylan Enjoy Queen at Siberia…, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0092)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Side 1: Score for a Lunch / Side 2: Dora Reese + Bob Dylan Enjoy Queen at Siberia 10 Cent Show
    - Title: Untitled, Unknown (Box 22, Folder ID: 156.0093)
    - Title: AC Singing, Unknown (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0094)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) AC Singing
    - Title: Street Noise '79, 1979 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0095)
      Capacity: 46 minutes
      Annotations: (on container:) Street Noise 79 / (on cassette:) A: "erase it" B: Street Noise
    - Title: [1]-- Jackie Song [2]-- Drive Drivel; 1974 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0096)
      Annotations: (on container:)Jackie song-Drive drivel 74/(on cassette:)A:Some weird voice I heard driving thru Colo.In somebody else's florist truck./ B:Winter '74 Jackie comes to visit + we sing some oldtime songs
    - Title: [1]-- Driving Drivel '74 [2]-- Vermonters talking…, 1974 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0097)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) 1. Eric-VT. Vermonters talking about it. Winter'74. J Morse,Rachel, Eric // 2: May'74 Brief driving Drivel + Duet of selves + Nov '74 Additives Last 243 #'s.
    - Title: [1]-- Inter Pyrex…1974 [2]-- Sunday Filler, Youngblood, Big Wheel (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0098)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: Inter Pyrex Vibrational Action Feb '74 // B: Jan '74, Sunday [Filler], Youngblood, Big Wheel
    - Title: Leon in Muncie, Coffee; Summer '73, 1973 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0099)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: Leon in Muncie Coffee: Summer 73 // B: Most Garbage don't bother
    - Title: [1]-- Bear Mountain [2]-- Air View of Siberia, Unknown (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0100)
      Annotations: (on container:) Bear MTN/ Siberia // (on cassette:) 0-222 Bear Mountain -373 air view of Siberia
    - Title: Solo exploration of Telluride, Colorado - circa 1973, 1973 or 1974 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0101)
      Annotations: (on container: Colorado 73 or 4 // (on cassette:) Solo exploration of Telluride, Colo.
    - Title: Road Words, Unknown (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0102)
      Annotations: (on container:) Road Words // (on cassette:) Road Thoughts poetic 4-5 / burned arm-road jet trail-highway from air plane
    - Title: [1]-- Brick Howls Household - sound collection [2]-- Pulminary Disruptions, Al Libke, Unknown (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0103)
      Annotations: (oncassette:) Brick Howls household sound collection // B: Pulminary Disruptions, Al Libke
    - Title: Street Noise, Unknown (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0104)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) A: Street noise (crossed out "F/A Sound") // B: Street Noise
    - Title: Water, [1974] (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0105)
      Annotations: (on container:) Water / GB-Duka-AC 74 // (on cassette:) A: Early water / B: Water GB/AC/DUKA
    - Title: AC Teaching Watercolor, Unkown (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0106)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) AC Teaching watercolor
    - Title: [1]-- Rapallo [2]-- Florence, Unknown (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0107)
      Annotations: (On cassette:) A: Plat(?) Rapallo / B: Florence
- Series XI: Film
  Film materials consist of production elements for media works by Callard and documentation of works by others. Access copies may not be available yet. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Film access copies may not be available for all material. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
    - Flourescent/ Azalea, a film by Andrea Callard (2009 Restoration), 1976 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0153)
      Gauge: 16mm, color, sound
    - 11 thru 12, a film by Andrea Callard (2009 Restoration), 1977 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0152)
    - Flora Funera - Answer Print (2011 Restoration) (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0172)
    - Lost Shoe Blues - Answer Print (2011 Restoration) (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0167)
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - Outside Noticing, Jan. 1976, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0108)
      Alternate title: [children with microphone]
      Gauge: Super8mm
      Footage count: [200 ft.]
      Extent: 1/1
      Annotations: "Outside Noticing" Jan '76
    - Untitled, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0109)
      Footage count: [400 ft.]
    - [1]-- Lost Shoe Blues [2]-- Flora Funera (For Battery Park City, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0110)
      18 fps
      Annotations: Unknown
      Alternate Title: [Untitled - Landscape with Different Plants]
    - New Jersey Night Fish; [1]--A Jumpery [2]--Rubber Glove Plays Ruler Piano For Measuring Mind [2a]--Flower/Azalea + By Stratch [3]--A Jimps In Cadeana, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0111)
      Alternate title: [New Jersey Night Fish]
    - [1]-- A asks if she can get 2 something to drink [ 2]-- Race cars [3]--. Sunglasses [4]-- Truck + pool in Muncie, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0112)
      Alternate title: Bathtub Movie
      Annotations: 1. A asks if she can get 2 something to drink - Brick + STEAM / 2. Race cars/ 3. Sunglasses/ 4. Truck + pool in Muncie // Bath tub movie / dog in truck/ Fred's sound recording experiments
    - Silent Selections, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0113)
      Footage count: [100 ft.]
      Annotations: Silent Selections
    - [1]-- Fake Beach [2]-- East River Dump [3]-- Dead Fish [4]-- Broken Glass + Ice [5]-- Bells [6]-- Firecrackers, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0114)
      Alternate title: [Some Food Maybe Found in the Dessert]
      Annotations: Reshoot Trash sequence w Kodachrome - get scratched feet repaired - add words to sound: Fake Beach; East River Dump; Dead Fish; Broken Glass + Ice; Bells; Firecrackers (Some Good May Be Found In The Desert)
    - Untitled, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0115)
      Alternate Title: [Air Travel; Nicaragua and/or USSR]
    - #3, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0116)
      Annotations: Date: #3
    - Utah MRM, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0117)
      Annotations: Utah MRM
    - Untitled, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0118)
      Alternate title: [Untitled - Flowers on Trees]
    - Untitled, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0119)
      Annotations: (on reel:) Reel 2
      Alternate title: [Untitled - Painting and Firedrill]
    - Ailanthus Film Samples, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0120)
      Annotations: 5645 // A. Callard Ailanthus Film Samples (print) Box 37 NYC 10013 212 925-8974
    - Florida, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0121)
      Annotations: Florida - Orig
    - 11 thru 12, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0122)
      Footage count: [200 ft]
      Annotations: 11 - 12 Super 8mm ^ 160 feet. Orig. // feature // 4257
    - Untitled, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0123)
      Annotations: same as 156.0122
      Alternate title: "Andrea Callard Notes on Ailanthus 10 Min. 18 Frames No Sound"
    - Untitled, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0124)
    - Red Film, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0125)
      Footage count: [150 ft.]
      Annotations: Red Film
    - Standard Adult Wheelchar; Temporary Participation For An Analogous Situation, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0126)
      Annotations: Standard Adult Wheelchar; Temporary Participation For An Analogous Situation; Super 8, sound, color, 18 FPS ^6 minutes running time
    - Alfred Hitchcock's Psycho, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0127)
      Annotations: Alfred Hitchcock's Psycho / Castle Films
    - Ekta Underwater, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0128)
      Footage count: [50 ft.]
      Annotations: Ekta Underwater
    - Hostage Parade - Street thru Roof, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0129)
      Annotations: [Geller] Hostage Parade - street thru roof
    - Silent Hostage Trash Ends, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0130)
      Annotations: Callard Silent Hostage Trash Ends
    - 360, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0131)
      Annotations: 360
    - [1]--Bay Bridge [2]-- Crossing Water [3]-- Eucalyptus [4]-- Lamp Reflect [5]-- Fog, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0132)
      Annotations: Bay Bridge; Crossing Water; Eucalyptus; Lamp Reflect; Fog
    - Beach Birds 76/77, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0133)
      Alternate title: [11 thru 12 outtakes]
      Annotations: Beach Birds 76 77
    - Wires: Linera Division of Landscape, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0134)
      Annotations: Wires: Linera Division of Landscape
    - Gull Takes Off, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0135)
      Annotations: Gull Takes Off
    - Water Tower Workers, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0136)
      Annotations: Water Tower Workers
    - Dog Play, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0137)
      Footage count: [25 ft.]
      Annotations: Dog Play
    - 1 Water Tower, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0138)
      Annotations: 1 Water Tower
    - [1]-- Portotino [2]-- Water [3]-- Lion [4]-- Commie [5]-- Clouds, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0139)
      Annotations: 4 Portotino; Water; Lion; Commie; Clouds
    - Bodies at Leisure, Ch. Beach '79, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0140)
      Annotations: Bodies at Leisure, Ch. Beach 79
    - Hostage Parade, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0141)
      Annotations: Hostage Parade
    - Water Exp., (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0142)
      Annotations: Water exp
    - F/A, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0143)
      Annotations: F/A
    - Delaware Stone Throw; July 4, 1975, (date of film) (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0144)
      Annotations: Delaware Stone Throw 4 July '75
- Oversize
  Oversize material is arranged by series. The folder number relates the folder to the material's location in the larger collection sequence.
  - Series I Subseries A: Colab Administrative materials
    - Andrea Callard's secretarial notebook; miscellaneous fragments, loose., undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Money disbursement and budget, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Series I Subseries B: Colab Shows and Events
    - Animals Living in Cities at Fashion Moda. poster, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Times Square Show advertisements. June 1980 at 7th Avenue and 41st St. (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Three Times Square Show posters by Reese Williams., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Times Square Show Poster by Jane Dickson and Charlie Ahearn, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Times Square Show press, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Animals Living in Cities at ABC NO RIO. newsprint announcement. Includes AC drawing from Ailanthus project., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Teu-Gum Show Poster. Geneva Switzerland., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - "Colab Hits the Ritz" poster. Colaboration between Colab and the Washington Project for the Arts. Washington DC., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Metropolis M german language periodical, no 4 November 1983. "Colab Kunst en de Lower East Side" (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - A. More Store advertisement in Artforum, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Up with People: An exhibition of graphics. 8 December-7 January at Concord Gallery NYC., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Poster: White Columns Interactive Video Screening Party. Includes Potato Wolf., undated (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Series II Subseries B: Andrea Callard Artist Files 1973-1976, 150 Chambers St.
    - Experiences Vacuume. Black and white photographs. (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Charting the Siberian Mountains., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - AC in costume. Black and white photographs., 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - notes for "A Dressing Wall" work., 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - Red Anger Association. Polaroid photographs in cardboard frame., 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 128)
    - Miscellaneous pencil drawings. no specific dates. located temorally through photographs as ca. 1973-1976. (Box 12, Folder 138)
    - background drawing, white paper and black ink., 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Page of art notebook, coffee and pencil. "a relaxed hand would not make such marks...", 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Series II Subseries C: Andrea Callard Artist Files, 1976-1978 40 Lispenard St.
    - City canoe black and white photos with captions., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Ciy Canoe black and white photographs, rejects and printing information., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Bat pamphlet original. AC's contribution to Colab's batman show in Robin Winters loft 591 Broadway., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Black and White still from "Standard Adult Wheelchair: Temporary participation for an analogous situation", 1977 (Box 13, Folder 163)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Cummington, MA: exposed pipe, building interior., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Andrea Callard and Fred Krughoof mind/heart photo collages., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Ailanthus Questionnaires, blank., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - Completed Ailanthus Questionnaires., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - Ailanthus Grove main plan. Black and white photos with hand coloring in large display book. Loose images and envelope of captions. Copyright September 1978. (Box 14, Folder 187)
      Metal, photographs sleeved in brittle plastic.
    - Ailanthus Grove main plan. Black and white photos with hand coloring. Loose images only. Copyright September 1978. (Box 13, Folder 187B)
    - Ailanthus, spraypaint and stencil with caption "Concentrate on Joy/ Nature is the boss/ Let's cross-polinate", 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - Ailanthus and trashbags, watercolor, 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - Color photographs of Ailanthus and cynthia moths with text on clear plastic overlay, 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - Gridded paper with captions, glue marks and pencil. Used for Ailanthus projects., 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 196)
    - Ailanthus black and white contact sheets., 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 197)
    - The Ailanthus family spread, Black and white hand tinted photographs with elictrical tape., 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 198)
    - Ailanthus drawings, 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 199)
  - Series II Subseries D: Andrea Callard Artist Files, 1979-1981 40 Lispenard St.
    - "All Animals Need Water to Survive" Andrea Callard's contribution to Colab's "Animals Living in the City" show.Color photographs on paper with text. Original, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Ailanthus project, Seed machine photograph., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Andrea Callard's proposal photo collages for the Custom and Culture II show, organized by Creative Time, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 211)